<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>

<!--
   New Perspectives on XML
   Tutorial 3
   Review Assignments

   Austin Technical College information technology degree list
   Author:  Tony Ruiz Ormeno
   Date:    6/10/23

   Filename:           degrees.xml
   Supporting Files:   degrees.xsd
-->



<degrees xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="degrees.xsd">
         
   <degree degreeID="IT10-152-100" degreeCode="MP">
      <title>Information Technology-Mobile Programmer</title>
      <approvalDate>2019-01-12</approvalDate>
      <effectiveDate>2019-09-01</effectiveDate>
      <summary>This two-year program meets the specific skill and knowledge requirements
	of technical and professional jobs within the information technology field for
	an entry-level mobile programmer working in a small to medium size
	organization. Training blends general educational development with required
	IT technical skills. Emphasis is in mobile web and application development.
      </summary>
      <coordinator>Janis Wu</coordinator>
      <comment date="2019-01-12">Janis Wu contacted regards heads up on approval.  Official paperwork is being sent</comment>
      <comment date="2019-01-01">Janis Wu assigned as coordinator</comment>
      <comment date="2018-12-01">Application draft submitted</comment>
   </degree>

    <degree degreeID="IT10-152-200" degreeCode="SP">
      <title>Information Technology-Software Programmer</title>
      <approvalDate>2017-12-12</approvalDate>
      <effectiveDate>2018-09-01</effectiveDate>
      <summary>This two-year program meets the specific skill and knowledge requirements of technical and 
      	professional jobs within the information technology field for an entry-level software programmer.
	Training meets the educational needs for most segments of the IT field, which primarily utilize
	small to midsize computers in conjunction with web and server applications. Emphasis is in LAMP and
	object-oriented languages. 
      </summary>
      <coordinator>Taylor Wapner</coordinator>
      <comment date="2019-06-12">Updates are being sent for approval</comment>
      <comment date="2018-12-01">Taylor Wapner assigned as coordinator</comment>
      <comment date="2017-12-12">Phil Bean contacted regards heads up on approval.  Official paperwork is being sent</comment>
      <comment date="2017-06-01">Phil Bean assigned as coordinator</comment>
      <comment date="2017-06-01">Application draft submitted</comment>
   </degree>
   
   <degree degreeID="IT10-152-300" degreeCode="WPA">
      <title>Information Technology-Web Programmer/Analyst</title>
      <approvalDate>2017-12-12</approvalDate>
      <effectiveDate>2018-09-01</effectiveDate>
      <summary>The Web Programmer/Analyst program meets the specific skill and knowledge requirements 
      	of technical and professional jobs within the information technology field for an entry-level Web 
      	analyst/programmer. It is designed to meet entry-level educational needs of most segments of 
      	the IT field which utilize a variety of computers. Training blends general educational development 
      	and required IT technical skills. Graduates are prepared for entry-level web developer jobs in 
      	government, insurance, manufacturing, service, software development, wholesale and retail 
      	sales, utilities, banking, and accounting.
      </summary>
      <coordinator>Christiana Sanchez</coordinator>
      <comment date="2018-12-01">Christiana Sanchez assigned as coordinator</comment>
      <comment date="2017-12-12">Taylor Wapner contact regards heads up on approval.  Official paperwork is being sent</comment>
      <comment date="2017-06-01">Taylor Wapner assigned as coordinator</comment>
      <comment date="2017-06-01">Application draft submitted</comment>
   </degree>
   
</degrees>